Guide to the Yale Athletics Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Football lantern slides, circa 1915; Accession 2008-A-065
  - 50 lantern slides, circa 1915 (Box 1–2)
    Due to the physical nature of the material in Accession 2008-A-065, Boxes 1-2, staff supervision is required for patron use in the reading room.
- Additional material, 1914; Accession 2015-A-044
  - Cartoon by Wallace Goldsmith of the first Yale-Harvard football game played at the Yale Bowl on November 21, 1914., 1914 November (Box 1)
- Photographs of Yale Freshman and Varsity Track Teams, 1906-1908; Accession 2017-A-060
  - Freshman track team group photograph, with Robert A. Riley identified, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - Varsity track team group photograph, with Robert A. Riley identified, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Photographs of Yale Men's Football Team, 1938-1940; Accession 2017-A-067
  - Collage of Yale Men's Football Team, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Collage of Yale Men's Football Team, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Men's Football photographs, 1938-1940 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - News clippings, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 2)